gooyaabitemplates.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Policy • Blogger Templates

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**What information do we collect?**

  * We collect Email Address from you when you subscribe to our newsletter and New Published Templates.
  * When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. however, You may visit our site anonymously.

**How do we protect your information?**

  * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the [safety](https://gooyaabitemplates.com/safety-blogger-template/) of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, http://gooyaabitemplates.com/ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. **Cookies and Web Beacons**

http://gooyaabitemplates.com/ does not use cookies. **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://gooyaabitemplates.com/.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://gooyaabitemplates.com/ and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.htmlSome of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use [technology](https://gooyaabitemplates.com/blogger-templates/technology/) to the advertisements and links that appear on http://gooyaabitemplates.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://gooyaabitemplates.com/ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://gooyaabitemplates.com/’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not abuse your any data including your emails and it’s always secured by us. We do not publish Designer, Author and User Details except Accepted by you to publish. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our [business](https://gooyaabitemplates.com/blogger-templates/business/), or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. **Third party links** Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any [feedback](https://gooyaabitemplates.com/feedback/) about these sites. **Terms and Conditions** Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://gooyaabitemplates.com/terms-service/>

**Your Consent**

  * By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

  * If we decide to change our privacy policy, which may be updated by us from any time without notice to you. You can check out Privacy Policy at any time at: [https://gooyaabitemplates.com/privacy-policy/](https://gooyaabitemplates.com/terms-service/ "Privacy Policy").
  * If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact](https://gooyaabitemplates.com/contact/) Admin by email at vsvmva@gmail.com.
